<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SPSS on Ritika Upadhyay</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/spss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SPSS on Ritika Upadhyay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Ritika Upadhyay &amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/spss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Analysis of Factors Influencing WhatsApp Usage Among Healthcare Professionals in India, May 2018</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/statistical-analysis-of-factors-influencing-whatsapp-usage-among-healthcare-professionals-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/statistical-analysis-of-factors-influencing-whatsapp-usage-among-healthcare-professionals-in-india/</guid>
      <description>The aim here was to better understand how healthcare professionals in India use WhatsApp to communicate with patients and which factors set apart those who do from those do do not. This study was a step towards a better understanding of benefits, risks and challenges pertaining to WhatsApp usage by healthcare professionals in India, leading to better use of such technological tools in healthcare.   Some interesting findings:  ● A healthcare professional having a separate SIM card/mobile device for wrk was more likely to interact with a patient using WhatsApp  ● If they encounter issues with storing healthcare information transmitted using WhatsApp, they seem significantly less likely to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Analysis of e-Visit Availability among respondents to Minnesota HIT Clinic Survey 2016, May 2018</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/statistical-analysis-of-e-visit-availability-among-respondents-to-minnesota-hit-clinic-survey-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/statistical-analysis-of-e-visit-availability-among-respondents-to-minnesota-hit-clinic-survey-2016/</guid>
      <description>Used logistic regression to assess which factors distinguish clinics in MN that offer patients e-Visit facilities, and the extent to which they do. Some key findings: ● Primary-care clinics are more likely to offer e-Visits than specialist clinics  ● Facilities that use Epic EHR systems are significantly likely to offer e-Visit facilities</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>